All right, so this
is all you need
to do to edit
this demo video. Have
a watch to this.
Lesson number three. Do
you have a hero?
Someone you really admire?
I did, and I
couldn't believe it when
they started to DM
me. In fact, I've
seen creators with 400
views on a video
land giant corporations as
clients, and Hollywood directors
comment on small channels
about screenplays. So right
now, you might be
looking at views thinking
they're small, but you
never know who's watching.
So lesson number three
is to treasure every
view you get, because
you only need one
to change your life,
and I see this
happen way more than
channels blowing up. Lesson
number four. Right, so
you see that? When
I said lesson number
X, all that happened
was the lesson number
filled the screen on,
it's kind of a
boring gray background. You
can use a color
block if you like.
Don't do anything too
crazy. Just keep it
simple. And then when
you make the lesson,
watch this. You just
put the short version
of the lesson on
screen down the bottom,
which guess what? You
already wrote during your
planning. So if you've
got an editor, what
you can do is
you can just send
them that list and
say, put that lesson.
At the end of
the lesson, and then
put the lesson number
at the start of
another one. I've also
linked to my versions
of these videos below,
so you can send
that to your editor
and go, this is
all I want. But
there's also two more
quick editing rules here
for this style of
video I want you
to follow. So firstly,
absolutely any time you
make a claim that
you got a result
or for someone else,
try and show proof
of that claim. So
if you're talking about
revenue increasing, put your
Stripe screenshot that proves
it. If you're talking
about growing a following,
put a graph. If
you're talking about client
wins, screenshot their email
where they're like, this
happened. Because if you
can't show proof, why
would anyone believe you?
Now, it's not always
possible, but if you
look at my videos,
I'm obsessed with putting
proof on the screen.
Because when someone watches
10 of your videos
in a row in
our system and sees
proof every time, it
builds insane trust. And
that has made the
biggest difference in my
business. And then the
next thing in the
edit is I need
you to keep the
tone real. So this
basically is your backstory
told through lessons learned.
So it's all about
being authentic. And that
means no fancy edits,
ban your editor from
doing random zooms and
jump cuts and things
that are fast. Don't
use flashy graphics every
five seconds. Just keep
it simple because that's
all this format needs.
All right, so go
get it edited or
hire an editor, and
then we're going to
post it. But after
that, we'll also do
a bit of measurement
and emotion control because
this is probably going
to flop. It won't
make you a millionaire,
even though you spent
four or five hours
on it. I'm sorry.
So, yeah, I'm going
to show you how
to do that.